Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Bobo, Willie - Tomorrow is here, 1977; SR-11971; Bobo, Willie (Box 193)
          Catalog # BN-LA711-G; A-side Matrix # BNLA-711-1
          Blue Note
        - Bocato - Sonho de um anarquista, 1987; SR-11972; Bocato (Box 193)
          Catalog # BA 034; A-side Matrix # BA-034-A
          Baratos Afins
          São Paulo, Brazil
        - Bocato - Ao vivo aqui jazz Brazil, 1989; SR-11973; Bocato (Box 193)
          Catalog # BA 044; A-side Matrix # BA-044-A
        - Bocato - Ladrão de trombone, 1990; SR-11974; Bocato (Box 193)
          Catalog # BA-048; A-side Matrix # BA-048-A
        - B.O.D. - We're here now; Streets never change, 1997; SR-11975; B.O.D. (Box 193)
          Catalog # 627791; A-side Matrix # 627791 A
          Gentry Entertainment
        - Body - Middle of the night, 1987; SR-11976; Body (Box 193)
          Catalog # MCA-23759; A-side Matrix # MCA-7130-FDS-2
        - Body - Middle of the night, 1987; SR-11977; Body (Box 193)
          Catalog # L33-17419; A-side Matrix # MCA 7405 FDS-2
        - Body - Have your cake, 1985; SR-11978; Body (Box 193)
          Catalog # POS 12-501; A-side Matrix # POS-12-501-A-5004-1
          Posse Records
        - Body and Soul - Dance to the drummer's beat, 1989; SR-11979; Body and Soul (Box 193)
          Catalog # DV 1007; A-side Matrix # DV-1007-A
          Delicious Vinyl
        - Body and Style - Listen to my cries, 1989; SR-11980; Body and Style (Box 193)
          Catalog # MIC 515AS; A-side Matrix # MIC-515 A
          Micmac Records
        - Body Shop - Never, 1979; SR-11981; Body Shop (Box 193)
          Catalog # DSC 139; A-side Matrix # RPM-D1001-AS
          Buddah Records
        - Bodyrock - Groove with you tonight; Crush sounds, 1994; SR-11982; Bodyrock (Box 194)
          Catalog # PRO-7425-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7425-A-2
        - Bofill, Angela - Teaser, 1983; SR-11983; Bofill, Angela (Box 194)
          Catalog # AL 8 8198; A-side Matrix # A-8-8198-S-1
          Artista
        - Bofill, Angela - Special delivery, 1983; SR-11984; Bofill, Angela (Box 194)
          Catalog # ADP-9186; A-side Matrix # ADP-9186A-1
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - The groove machine/the boogie train, 1979; SR-11985; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # MK-105; A-side Matrix # MK-105-A-TH2
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Insides out, 1975; SR-11986; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # DK 76916; A-side Matrix # D-128-1C
          Dakar Records
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Let's start the dance III, 1983; SR-11987; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # CPD-204; A-side Matrix # CPD-204-83CP-2054-PRC-C1-1-1-A
          Compleat Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - I've got the dance fever, 1982; SR-11988; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # 4Z9 02876; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-02876-3
          Phase II Records, Ltd
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Dance, dance, dance all night; April my love part I, 1980; SR-11989; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # 4W8 5652; A-side Matrix # 4W8-5652-AS
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Foot stompin' in the summertime, 1981; SR-11990; Bohannon, Hamilton; Caroline (Box 194)
          Catalog # 4W8 02146; A-side Matrix # 4W8-02146-AS X
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Don't be ashame to call my name, 1981; SR-11991; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # AS 919; A-side Matrix # AS-919-AS-RE-1 X
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Make your body move, 1983; SR-11992; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # CPD-201; A-side Matrix # CPD-201-A
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Dance fever greatest hits, 1986; SR-11993; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # ARS 10.017; A-side Matrix # ARS 10017-A1
          ARS Records
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Cut loose, 1979; SR-11994; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-11995. Different discs
          Catalog # MDS-3002; A-side Matrix # MDS-3002-2-54970-A8-CP
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Cut loose; The beat (part 2), 1979; SR-11995; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-11994. Different discs
          Catalog # MK-77; A-side Matrix # TI MK-77-A1-CT
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - Alive, 1981; SR-11996; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          Catalog # 22L0306; A-side Matrix # 22L0306A
          Victoria
          Spain
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - The Bohannon drive, 1983; SR-11997; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-11998. 2 copies
          Catalog # CPL-1-1005; A-side Matrix # CPL-1-1005-A-PRP-1
        - Bohannon, Hamilton - The Bohannon drive, 1983; SR-11998; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-11997. 2 copies
        - Bohemia - No ordinary move, 1983; SR-11999; Bohemia (Box 194)
          Catalog # R11129; A-side Matrix # R-11129-A
          Discos De Tinga
        - Bôkaye' - Ethno groove, 1994; SR-12000; Bôkaye' (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12001. 2 copies
          Catalog # NMX 070; A-side Matrix # MNX 070 A
          New Music International
        - Bôkaye' - Ethno groove, 1994; SR-12001; Bôkaye' (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12000. 2 copies
        - Bold, J - Transatlantic accent EP, SR-12002; Bold, J (Box 194)
          Catalog # CHAMP001; A-side Matrix # CHAMP001-A2
          Championship Vinyl
        - Bolland, CJ - Sugar is sweeter, 1996; SR-12003; Bolland, CJ (Box 194)
          Catalog # 697-120 102-1; A-side Matrix # 697-120-102-1 A
          FFRR
        - Bollock Brothers - Horror movies, 1985; SR-12004; Bollock Brothers (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12005. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # CEL 0162; A-side Matrix # CEL0162A
        - Bollock Brothers - Horror movies, 1985; SR-12005; Bollock Brothers (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12004. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Bolton, Amy - What does it take; Kicks, 1982; SR-12006; Bolton, Amy (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12007. 2 copies
          Catalog # MP-314; A-side Matrix # MP-314-A
          Importe/12 Records
        - Bolton, Amy - What does it take; Kicks, 1982; SR-12007; Bolton, Amy (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12006. 2 copies
        - Bolton, Amy - Do me a favor, 1980; SR-12008; Bolton, Amy (Box 194)
          Catalog # MP-309; A-side Matrix # MP-309-A
        - Bolton, Michael - (Sitiin' on) the dock of the bay, 1987; SR-12009; Bolton, Michael (Box 194)
          Catalog # CAS 1028; A-side Matrix # XSS-177636-DMM-1A
        - Bomb the Bass - Say a little prayer (Limited edition remix), 1988; SR-12010; Bomb the Bass; Maureen (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12011. 2 copies
          Catalog # Torso 12089; A-side Matrix # 08 24545 1A1
          Torso
        - Bomb the Bass - Say a little prayer (Limited edition remix), 1988; SR-12011; Bomb the Bass; Maureen (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12010. 2 copies
        - Bomb Squad - Future, 1997; SR-12012; Bomb Squad; BBC Click (Box 194)
          Catalog # CR-406; A-side Matrix # CR-406-A
          Cutting Traxx
        - Bomb the Bass - Winter in July, 1991; SR-12013; Bomb the Bass (Box 194)
          Catalog # DOOD 6TP; A-side Matrix # DOOD6TP A
        - Bomb the Bass - Bug Powder Dust, 1996; SR-12014; Bomb the Bass (Box 194)
          Catalog # 162-531 068-1; A-side Matrix # 162-531 068-1AS -HS
          Quango Records
        - Bomb the Bass - Beat dis, 1988; SR-12015; Bomb the Bass (Box 194)
          Catalog # PRO 462; A-side Matrix # PRO462A
          4th & Broadway
        - Bomb the Bass - One to one religion, 1995; SR-12016; Bomb the Bass (Box 194)
          Catalog # 162-531 047-1; A-side Matrix # 162-531 047-1A
        - Bombay Jungle - Hindi mixes, 1994; SR-12017; Bombay Jungle (Box 194)
          Catalog # ARLP 7008; A-side Matrix # ARLP 7008 A1
          2Kool
        - Bombers - The Mexican; Dance, dance, dance, 1978; SR-13322; Bombers (Box 194)
          Catalog # WES 12112; A-side Matrix # WES 12112-70326
          West End Records
        - B.O.N. - Boys almighty remixes, 2000; SR-12018; B.O.N. (Box 194)
          Catalog # EAS 16459; A-side Matrix # XSS-16459-A
        - Bon Rock & The Rythem Rebellion - Searching rap, 1981; SR-13323; Bon Rock & The Rythem Rebellion (Box 194)
          Catalog # 1001; A-side Matrix # 567-A-PRI-2
          Reelin & Rockin Records
        - Bones, Frankie - Bonesbreaks 10, 1995; SR-12019; Bones, Frankie (Box 194)
          Catalog # HAL 12649; A-side Matrix # HAL-12649-A
          Breaking Bones Records
        - Bones, Frankie - Volume 2 - raw beats for DJ's, 1988; SR-12020; Bones, Frankie; Bonesbreaks (Box 194)
          Catalog # AP 135; A-side Matrix # AP-135-A
          Underworld Records
        - Bones, Frankie - Volume 5 - the original raw & raunchy beats for DJ's, 1990; SR-12021; Bones, Frankie; Bonesbreaks (Box 194)
          Catalog # AP 144; A-side Matrix # AP144-A
        - Bones, Frankie - Bone up!, 1995; SR-12022; Bones, Frankie (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12023. 2 copies
          Catalog # TX 5034; A-side Matrix # TX5034A
        - Bones, Frankie - Bone up!, 1995; SR-12023; Bones, Frankie (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12022. 2 copies
        - Bon Rock - Junior wants to play, 1982; SR-12024; Bon Rock; Cotton Candy (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12025. 2 copies
          Catalog # TB822; A-side Matrix # TB-822-I
          Staten Island, New York
        - Bon Rock - Junior wants to play, 1982; SR-12025; Bon Rock; Cotton Candy (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12024. 2 copies
        - Bond TCK - Let me take you home, 1988; SR-12026; Bond TCK (Box 194)
          Catalog # POS 1232; A-side Matrix # POS 1232 A
        - RIP Bondz - Shorty in my life, 2004; SR-12027; RIP Bondz (Box 194)
          Catalog # BBM 024; A-side Matrix # BBM 024-A
          Big Brother Music
        - Bone Crusher - Never scared (the takeover remix); Back up, 2003; SR-12028; Bone Crusher (Box 194)
          Catalog # 82876-53221-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-53221-1SA RJ
          Break 'Em Off Records
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - X-tasy, 2000; SR-12029; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # RPROLP4335; A-side Matrix # RPROLP 4335A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - E. 1999 eternal, 1995; SR-12030; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # 88561-5539-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-5539-1-A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - E. 1999 eternal (phukkin clean version), 1995; SR-12031; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # RPROLP 0392; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0392-A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - Thuggish-ruggish-bone, 1994; SR-12032; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # 88561-6627-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-5527-1 A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - Days of our livez, 1996; SR-12033; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # ED-5871; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5871-A2
          Eastwest Records
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - The art of war (Disc one), 1997; SR-12034; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12035. Double album
          Catalog # 88561-6340-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6340-1 A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - The art of war (Disc two), 1997; SR-12035; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          In same jacket as # SR-12034. Double album
          Catalog # 88561-6340-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6340-1 C
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - Change the world, 2000; SR-12036; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 194)
          Catalog # EAS 15221; A-side Matrix # XSS-15221-A 1A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - East 1999, 1995; SR-12037; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0415; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0415A
        - Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) - War, 1998; SR-12038; Bone Thugs-n-harmony (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # WAR 1 S 38726
          Dreamworks Records
        - Bones, Frankie - Bonesbreaks 2000, 2000; SR-12039; Bones, Frankie (Box 195)
          Catalog # BMF001; A-side Matrix # BMF-001A
          Badmotherf#*ker
        - Bonk Combo - Car jam, 1983; SR-12040; Bonk Combo (Box 195)
          Catalog # PRO 7811; A-side Matrix # PRO-7811-A
        - Bonk - Car jam; Cupid in cars, 1983; SR-12041; Bonk (Box 195)
          Catalog # 12ENY 502; A-side Matrix # 12 ENY 502 A-1U-1-1
          Ensign
        - Bonobo - Full stop, 1997; SR-12042; Bonobo (Box 195)
          Catalog # DT 6500039; A-side Matrix # DT 65000039-A
          DJ Therapy
        - Boo - Say it to my face, 2005; SR-12043; Boo (Box 195)
          Catalog # J12-67158-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-67158-1SA
          J Records
        - Boo-Boo "B" - Boo-Boo's break; Jump, 1985; SR-12044; Boo-Boo "B" (Box 195)
          Catalog # CSR-905; A-side Matrix # CSR-905-That side
          Cobbler Records
          Narberth, Pennsylvania
        - Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. - R.A.I.D., 1989; SR-12045; Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. (Box 195)
          Catalog # BWAY 492; A-side Matrix # BWAY-492-A
        - Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. - Rumors of a dead man, 1992; SR-12046; Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. (Box 195)
          Catalog # ED 5619; A-side Matrix # STED5619-A2-DMM
          Hollywood BASIC
        - BooBlades - Da hottness; In love with a thug; Gangsta, SR-12047; BooBlades (Box 195)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # BWR-001-A
          Brainwave Records
        - Boodram, Sharlene - Calcutta woman, 1994; SR-12048; Boodram, Sharlene (Box 195)
          Catalog # JMC-1092; A-side Matrix # JMC1092A
          Jamaican Me Crazy Records
        - Boogerman - The Boogerman, 1992; SR-12049; Boogerman (Box 195)
          Catalog # PRO-7388; A-side Matrix # PRO-7388-A
        - Boogie Bass Bombers - Boogie bass, 1988; SR-12050; Boogie Bass Bombers (Box 195)
          Catalog # HAL 1283; A-side Matrix # HAL-1283-A JUAN
          Pop Music Records
        - Boogie Boys - You ain't fresh, 1985; SR-12051; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          Catalog # V-15207; A-side Matrix # V-1-15207-99849-A/C
        - Boogie Boys - You ain't fresh, 1985; SR-12052; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
        - Boogie Boys - City life; A fly girl, 1985; SR-12053; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12054. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-8645; A-side Matrix # V-8645-99850A-99846-Z1
        - Boogie Boys - City life; A fly girl, 1985; SR-12054; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12053. 2 copies
        - Boogie Boys - Zodiac; Break dancer; Shake and break, 1984; SR-12055; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12056. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-8578; A-side Matrix # V 8578 99187 A-99117 Z4
        - Boogie Boys - Zodiac; Break dancer; Shake and break, 1984; SR-12056; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12055. 2 copies
        - Boogie Boys - Share my world; Run it, 1986; SR-12057; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12058. Different discs
          Catalog # V-15265; A-side Matrix # V-1-15265-100256B-100262B-Z2
        - Boogie Boys - Girl talk, 1986; SR-12058; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12057. Different discs
          Catalog # V-15230; A-side Matrix # V-1-15230-100260-100260A-Z2
        - Boogie Boys - Runnin' from your love; Party asteroid, 1985; SR-12059; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          Catalog # V-15214; A-side Matrix # V-1-15214-Z1
        - Boogie Boys - I'm comin'; Romeo knight, 1987; SR-12060; Boogie Boys (Box 195)
          Catalog # V-15338; A-side Matrix # V-1-15338-100802A 1B 1950-Z-2
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - Man & his music (Disc one), 1988; SR-12061; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12062. Double album
          Catalog # BB 1-2000; A-side Matrix # BB 1-2000-A1
          B-Boy Records
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - Man & his music (Disc two), 1988; SR-12062; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12061. Double album
          Catalog # BB 1-2000; A-side Matrix # BB 1-2000-A2
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - My philosophy, 1988; SR-12063; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # 1096-1-JD; A-side Matrix # 1096-1-JD-A
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - We in there, 1992; SR-12064; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # 01241-42070-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42070-1-A1
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - Why is that?, 1989; SR-12065; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # 1231-1-JD; A-side Matrix # 1231-JD-A
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - Ya know the rules, 1990; SR-12066; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # 1415-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1415-1-JDA
        - Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) - Love's gonna get'cha (material love), 1990; SR-12067; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 195)
          Catalog # 1367-1-JD; A-side Matrix # 1367-1-JDA
        - Boogiemonsters - Honeydips in Gotham, 1995; SR-12068; Boogiemonsters (Box 195)
          Catalog # Y-58361; A-side Matrix # Y-58361-A-RE1
          Pendulum Records
        - Boogy, Sly - That's my name, 2004; SR-12069; Boogy, Sly (Box 195)
          Catalog # J1PV-59964-1; A-side Matrix # J1W-59964-1 SA
        - Book of Love - You make me feel so good, 1986; SR-12070; Book of Love (Box 195)
          Catalog # 0-20474; A-side Matrix # B-23884-SH2
        - Book of Love - Pretty boys and pretty girls; Tubular bells, 1988; SR-12071; Book of Love (Box 195)
          Catalog # 0-20963; A-side Matrix # B-31345-RE1SA1
        - Book of Love - Modigliani (lost in your eyes), 1986; SR-12072; Book of Love (Box 195)
          Catalog # 0-20650; A-side Matrix # 0-20650-A-SH1
        - Booker T & The MG's - Up tight, 1969; SR-12073; Booker T & The MG's (Box 195)
          Catalog # SXE 024; A-side Matrix # DMD-0961 A-1/10-89
        - Booker T & The MG's - McLemore avenue, 1970; SR-12074; Booker T & The MG's (Box 195)
          Catalog # SXE 016; A-side Matrix # DMC-4499 S-1/9-88 C
        - Bonzo Goes to Washington - 5 minutes, 1984; SR-12075; Bonzo Goes to Washington (Box 195)
          Catalog # SLX 666-13; A-side Matrix # SB 13 A M1
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Boom, Juny - Rules of the game, 1981; SR-13324; Boom, Juny (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-13325. 2 copies
          Catalog # SNO 500; A-side Matrix # SNO-500-A
          Snowflake
        - Boom, Juny - Rules of the game, 1981; SR-13325; Boom, Juny (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-13324. 2 copies
        - Boom Shaka - Creation, 1988; SR-12076; Boom Shaka (Box 195)
          Catalog # MT 018; A-side Matrix # MT-018-A
          Moving Target
        - Boomerang - These boots are made for walkin', 1986; SR-12077; Boomerang (Box 195)
          Catalog # DMD 993; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-50915-50916-1
        - Boomtown Rats - Up all night; Mood Mambo; Banana republic, 1981; SR-12078; Boomtown Rats (Box 195)
          Catalog # AS 920; A-side Matrix # XSM168480-1B
        - Boone Bros - (Perty people) throwdown, 1983; SR-12079; Boone Bros (Box 195)
          Catalog # DMD 607; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44294-1
        - Boone, Len - Love won't be denied, 1978; SR-12080; Boone, Len (Box 195)
          Catalog # CDS-2229; A-side Matrix # CDS-2229-AS
        - Bootleg - Fantasies, 1999; SR-12081; Bootleg (Box 195)
          Catalog # RPROLP0957; A-side Matrix # RPROLP 0957A
        - Bootman - Volume 5 - the original raw & raunchy beats for DJ's, 1995; SR-12082; Bootman (Box 195)
          Catalog # TNT-34; A-side Matrix # TNT-34-A
          TNT Records
        - Bootsy's Rubber Band - Body slam!, 1982; SR-12083; Bootsy's Rubber Band (Box 195)
          Catalog # 0-29919; A-side Matrix # 0-29919A-S
        - Bootsy's Rubber Band - The Pinocchio theory, 1977; SR-12084; Bootsy's Rubber Band (Box 195)
          Catalog # K 16964; A-side Matrix # K-16964-A-1
        - Bootsy's Rubber Band - Bootzilla, 1978; SR-12085; Bootsy's Rubber Band (Box 195)
          Catalog # K 17196; A-side Matrix # K17196-A
        - B.O.P. Entertainment - Rendition of soul (Disc one), 1998; SR-12086; B.O.P. Entertainment (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12087. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-420; A-side Matrix # SOW-420 A
        - B.O.P. Entertainment - Rendition of soul (Disc two), 1998; SR-12087; B.O.P. Entertainment (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12086. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-420; A-side Matrix # SOW-420 C
        - B.O.P. Entertainment - "Rendition of soul" Vol. 3 (Disc one), 2000; SR-12798; B.O.P. Entertainment (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12799. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-450; A-side Matrix # SOW-450-A
        - B.O.P. Entertainment - "Rendition of soul" Vol. 3 (Disc two), 2000; SR-12799; B.O.P. Entertainment (Box 195)
          In same jacket as # SR-12798. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-450; A-side Matrix # SOW-450-C
        - Bopol - Helena, SR-12088; Bopol; Innovation (Box 195)
          Catalog # Syllart 8310; A-side Matrix # SYLLART 8310 A
        - Boriqua Style - Boriqua Style, SR-12089; Boriqua Style (Box 195)
          Catalog # BBR 012-1; A-side Matrix # BBR-012A
          Bumble Beats Records
        - Born 2wice - Child 4 freestyle, 1991; SR-12090; Born 2wice (Box 195)
          Catalog # YO-9001-1; A-side Matrix # YO-9001
          Righteous Records
        - Born in August - April (the remix), 1996; SR-12091; Born in August (Box 196)
          Catalog # U8P 1055; A-side Matrix # U8P-1055-RE1
          Bystorm Entertainment
        - Born Jamericans - Yardcore, 1996; SR-12092; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # BJYC-A RE1
        - Born Jamericans - Warning sign, 1994; SR-12093; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          Catalog # DMD 2135; A-side Matrix # STDM-72219-72220-72221-1
        - Born Jamericans - Send my love, 1997; SR-12094; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          Catalog # DV1233-1; A-side Matrix # DV-1233-1 RE1
        - Born Jamericans - Yardcore (Disc one), 1997; SR-12095; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          In same jacket as # SR-12096. Double album
          Catalog # DV5018-1; A-side Matrix # DV 5018-1A
        - Born Jamericans - Yardcore (Disc two), 1997; SR-12096; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          In same jacket as # SR-12095. Double album
          Catalog # DV5018-1; A-side Matrix # DV 5018-1C
        - Born Jamericans - Sweet honey, 1994; SR-12097; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          Catalog # DMD 2162; A-side Matrix # STDM-2162A-1
        - Born Jamericans - 44 maggin' - the single, 1999; SR-12098; Born Jamericans (Box 196)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # T1-001-A
          44 Ways
        - Born Unoticed - Blood - n - tears, 1995; SR-12099; Born Unoticed (Box 196)
          Catalog # TT9501; A-side Matrix # TT 9501A
          N.O.T. Production
        - Bose - Don't knock it (till you try it), 1987; SR-12100; Bose (Box 196)
          Catalog # HAL 1249; A-side Matrix # HAL-1249-A
          Rockwell Records
        - Boss - I don't give a fuck; Mai sista izza bitch, 1992; SR-12101; Boss (Box 196)
          In same jacket as # SR-12102. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # 44 74374; A-side Matrix # XSS-74374-B-1A